Ryan Palmer

Nationality: American Date of birth: 13 Nov 1995 Gender: Male Phone number: (+1) 5133160505

Email address: ryanpnayr@gmail.com in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ryanpnayr/

Orlando, FL (United States)

ABOUT ME

Software engineer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Worked on 4 startup teams wearing many different hats. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering more than a decade of writing code and 7+ years of professional experience.

Education:

I had 4 years of Software Development education in high school. I then studied Computer Science for 7 semesters at the University of Cincinnati while working a full time Co-op at CIC IT Life from 2014-2016.

Skills:

Nodejs, ExpressJs, ReactJS, Angular, Material UI, JavaScript, Python, Kotlin, SASS, HTML, CSS, Flutter, Dart, React native, Postgres, Mongo, MySQL, SQLite, AWS, GCP, Linode, Netlify, Github, GitLab, RESTful apis, Web Development, API Integrations

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer

Level Technology [Apr 2022 - Mar 2023]

City: Seattle, WA

- Reviewed project specifications, designed and built out solutions for modern online banking for gig workers using Plaid, Unit, and Argyle. (React.js, Kotlin & Python)
- Built automated syncs for customer support for tools like Zendesk and Hubspot with our private systems.

Senior Software Engineer

Live Person/Tenfold [Jul 2021 – Jun 2022]

City: Austin, TX

- · Lead team of engineers to build out Tenfold's Webex phone integration. (MEAN Stack)
- Worked on a team constructing live transcriptions of agent calls to within our Salesforce integration.

Full Stack Software Engineer

Redeapp [Feb 2019 - Jul 2021]

City: Louisville, KY

- Lead Redeapp's Android development by building out, testing, and deploying changes for their messaging platform. (Kotlin & Java)
- Performed web app migration from Angular.js to modern angular and established end too end testing in cypress. (Angular.js, Angular 9+, Python)

Software Engineer

Level 12 [Jan 2018 - Feb 2019]

City: Jeffersonville, IN

- · Orchestrated projects within strict timeframes and budget constraints by updating/creating web apps. (Python, React)
- Maintained product quality by keeping at least 90% automated tests coverage.

Software integration engineer

Astronomer INC [Aug 2016 - Oct 2017]

City: Cincinnati, Ohio

- Created and maintained containerized Node.js integrations and libraries for Astronomers open sourced Analytics.js Platform. (Javascript, Node.js)
- Designed Airflow data pipelines written in Node.js and python connecting external data sources to databases sending up to millions of events with test coverage in Mocha, Chai, and Nock. (Python, Node.js)